Isaiah Hogan

760-686-4288| isaiah.hogan25@gmail.com | Melissa, TX | LinkedIn Isaiah Hogan

SUMMARY

Detail-oriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Java SE 8 Programmer I Certification (in progress; expected date of completion 08/2022)

- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Spring Boot
- Spring Data JPA
- Spring Security (JWT)

- Bootstrap
- REST API's
- SQL
- Unit Testing (JUnit, Mockito)
- SOLID OOP Principles
- Dependencies Injection
- Git
- GitHub

EXPERIENCE and TRAINING

Generation Junior_Full Stack Java Developer Program | April 2022- August 2022

Training Participant (in progress)

Currently participating in a 16 week Junior Full Stack Java Developer program spending over 460+ hours learning the technologies involved to create a full stack web application with Java using Spring Boot Framework, HTML5, CSS3, implementing basic unit tests and deploying the application to Heroku. Expected date of completion: August 2022.

EXPERIENCE

Barista Starbucks

August 2021 - February 2022 Starbucks, Anna, TX

- Greeted and served an average of 600+ customers daily, providing prompt, personalized, and friendly service in a fast-paced environment
- Performed all pre-shift and post-shift duties, side-work, and related manager support tasks weekly.
- Communicated effectively with all team members and customers resulting in consistent positive manager feedback
- Quickly learned the entire menu and preparation thereof resulting in a shortened onboarding time frame
- Trained new baristas in workflow procedures, barista expertise, and corporate brand sales techniques improving overall store sales results

Food Prep Champion

October 2020 - December 2020

Taco Bell, Melissa, TX

- Processed 200+ orders in one shift, maintaining the store service standards and increasing customer satisfaction feedback
- Consistently maintained compliance with company policies and procedures for food safety, sanitation and quality
- Accurately processed customer orders, cash and credit card payments
- Maintained consistent attendance and punctuality resulting in high dependability and increased responsibility

EDUCATION

May 2021 - High School Diploma, Melissa, TX